Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Anthropology Records 1929-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Alphabetical Files
  - Subseries 2: General Alphabetical Files
    - Survey, Miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Symposium on Northern Mississippi Valley Archeology, Department of Anthropology and Illinois State Museum, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - T, General, 1957, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Tax, Sol, Central States Anthropological Symposium, The Fox Indian Project, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Teaching of Anthropology, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, Hiram W. Lectures, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Time Schedules, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Travel, Division of Social Science, 1961, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Transfer of Credits, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Travel to Meetings (Tax Itinerary), 1960 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Tuition Schedules, 1957, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - United States- Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Public Health Service, 1960-1962, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - United States, Department of State, Survey and Report, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - United States Information Agency, Bi-National Cultural Center, undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - University of Chicago Library, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1961-1968 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - University of Michigan, Center for Tropical Studies, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - University Microfilms, 1964-1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - University Senate, Council, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - V, Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Vehicles, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Veteran Administration, 1951-1959 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam, 1968-1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - W, Miscellaneous, 1959-1961 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Wilkie Foundation, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program, 1958-1968 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Yucatan, Social Psychology Field Station (NSF Proposal), 1964 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 3: Wenner Gren Symposium on Anthropological PhD Curricula
    - Brown University, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1954-1957 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Catholic University, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Columbia University, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Cornell University, 1957, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Harvard University, 1956-1959 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Hartford University, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Indiana University, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles State College, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Michigan State University, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Northwestern University, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Stanford University, 1958, undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Syracuse University, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Yale University, 1958-1962 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - University of Arizona, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1958, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - University of Chicago, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - University of Colorado, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - University of Illinois, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - University of Kentucky, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - University of Michigan, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - University of Minnesota, 1956, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - University of New Mexico, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - University of North Carolina, 1955-1956, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - University of Oregon, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - University of Rochester, 1959-1965 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - University of Utah, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - University of Washington, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - University of Wisconsin- Madison, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Universities (Other), 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Universities, Directory, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Series IV: Microfilm
  - Subseries 1: Chiapas
    - INAH, Chiapas Series, Reels 1-2, 25, 51, 63-70, 78-9, 84-8, 91-2, 94-5, 108, undated (Box 37)
    - Middle American Cultural Anthropology, Fieldnotes on San Andras, Tuxtla by Betty Starr, Series 6, Item 33, undated (Box 37)
    - #10614, Teoposca, (J. Hotchkiss), Index and volume 1-2, undated (Box 37)
    - #10927, Ocosingo Field Noes by Rob. Montagu, Parts 1-2, Neg., 1961 (Box 37)
    - #10927, Part 2 Pos, Chamula Vocabulary, undated (Box 37)
    - #12060, Chiapas: Caro Baroja, Julio "the World of the Witches", undated (Box 37)
    - Neg 1694.15, MS. No 15, Arciniega, Monografia de Chamula, Ms #15, Pozas, undated (Box 37)
    - A1812, vocabularies, (1957-1958 Chiapas dialect Survey), 1957-1958 (Box 37)
    - A00909, pos. Mann, Ocosingo, May-April, undated (Box 37)
    - A011381, Mann, Ocosingo, March-September. undated (Box 37)
    - Index of Chiapas microfilm en Chapultepec, undated (Box 37)
    - Chanal (Medina, Verbitsky, Guiteas Holmes), Censos socio-culturales, Genealogies, Name Group combinations, First Report, Vocabularies, undated (Box 37)
    - Biblioteca de Palacio, Codice Sahagún (292), [nahuatl], undated (Box 37)
    - Chiapas, Archives, Baroco, undated (Box 37)
    - Censo General de la Población, Ocosingo, undated (Box 37)
    - Censo General, Ocosingo, undated (Box 37)
    - Deck, Dorothy, Mam Syntax (Box 37)
    - Tzotzil Dictionary, undated (Box 37)
    - Chiapas Project Field Notes, Venustiano Carranza(San Bartolome de los Llanos), Fieldworker: Marcelo Diaz de Salas, Negative, pp. 1-236, undated (Box 37)
    - Chamula Census, undated (Box 37)
    - Film Copies of Map of Tenejapa, Unsigned but probably made by Pedro Wakas in 1960, Copy Made November 1962 (Box 37)
    - Chiapas Project Field Notes, Villa las Rosas (Pinola). Field Worker Esther Hermitte, pp. 1-249, negative, August 19 to January 5, undated (Box 37)
    - Field Notes of Charles E. Mann on Ocosingo, undated (Box 37)
    - Chiapas Archeological Survey, Major sites visited, Adams, 1960 (Box 37)
    - Salovesh, M. Venustiano Carranza Field Notes, pp. 1-227, August 10-February 12, 1960-1961 (Box 37)
    - Hermitte, Esther, Charts, undated (Box 37)
    - Aguacatenango, Duane Metzger's Materials, linguistic Informant transcription, manuscript text #1, 9.60 (Box 37)
    - Barrera-Vazquez, Gramática Yucateca, 1946 (Box 37)
    - Neg 1694 20, Ms. No. 20, Notas sobre Zinacantan, Tax Field Party (?), undated (Box 37)
  - Subseries 2: Guatemala
    - AGI, Guatemala, 56, Roll 1-2 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 66, 98, 101, 102, 375- Roll 1 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 128, 224, (Huehuetenango) (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 293- Roll 1 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 293- Rolls 2 and 3 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 294- Roll 1 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 294- Roll 2 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 294- Roll 3 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 295- Rolls 1 and 2 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 295- Roll 3 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 295- Roll 4 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 295- Roll 5 [Missing] (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 296- Roll 1 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 296- Roll 2 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 375 (Roll 2), 110, 112, 117, Justicia, 183 Guatemala, 123, 58 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 386, 170, 971 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Guatemala, 44, 57 Justicia, 331 Guatemala, 61, 67 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Indiferente General 1342, Nos. 13 (Philippines), 14 (Peru), 16 (Colombia), 17 (Guatemala), 1788-1790 (Box 38)
    - AGI, Mexico 168, Guadalajara 51, Guatemala 52 (Reel 3- 63 Frames) (Box 38)
    - AGI, 9, 54, 170(Guatemala); 334B, 349C, 350A, 356 A (Escribania) (Box 38)
    - AGI, 334B (Escribania); 60 (Patronato) (Box 38)
    - AGI, Escribania, 345B (Box 38)
    - AGI,Contaduria, 970 (Rolls 1 and 2) (Box 38)
    - AGI, Contaduria, 972ª (Box 38)
    - Middle American Cultural Anthropology, Series 4, items 24/25, Dios Rosales (Box 38)
    - Middle American Cultural Anthropology, Arte de Las Tres Languas: Quiche, y...by P. Fr. Francisco Ximenez, Series 6, Item 36 (Box 38)
    - #5430, San Bartolo, Field Notes, Baroco, Rubell, Sadvesh (Box 38)
    - Vocabulario de Mayathan, Diccionario de Vienna (Box 38)
    - Day, Chris "the Phonology of Pinola Tzeltal", Chicago M.A. Paper, 1960 (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts on American Indian Cultural Anthropology, Series IX, No. 55. Kaufmann, Terrence S. Materials on Mayan Historical Linguistics, 1962 (Box 38)
    - Ara, Domingo de. Sermonario en Lengua Tzeltal, undated (Box 38)
    - Spoken Quiché, Structured Change Drills, undated (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts on Middle American Cultural Anthropology, Neg 1694.13, Ms. No. 13, Tax, The Towns of Lake Atitlan, undated (Box 38)
    - Neg 1694 16, Ms. No. 16, Tax, Notes on Santo Tomás Chichicastenango, undated (Box 38)
    - Neg 1694 17, Ms. No. 17, Goubaud, Rosales, Tax, Reconnaissance of Northern Guatemala, 1944 (Box 38)
    - Neg 1694 18, Ms. No. 18, Tax, Miscellaneous Notes on Guatemala, undated (Box 38)
    - Neg 1694 19, Ms. No. 19, Redfield and Tax, April is This Afternoon, undated (Box 38)
    - Middle American Cultural Anthropology, Ms. No 3, Neg. 1694.3 Redfield, Ms. No 4 Neg. 1694.4 Redfield (Box 38)
    - Middle American Cultural Anthropology, A Series of Theses and Research Papers, Series 6, Item 31 (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts on Middle American Cultural Anthropology No. 28: Charles Wisdom, "Materials on the Chorti Language", undated (Box 38)
  - Subseries 3: Fox
    - Fox Notes 1, Tax Field Notes and Genealogies, Indexed, Pp, 1-6098, pp. 1908-1990, Census 1948, 1932-1934 (Box 38)
    - Fox Notes 2, Journals, News Clippings, Correspondence, Indexed pp 1-1890, 1948-50 (Box 38)
    - Fox Notes 3, #49039, Additions to 48 Journals, Journals 1949-1951, pp. 1991-2247 (Box 38)
    - Fox Notes 4, Journals, pp. 39787-39881, 2248-2428, 1952-1953 (Box 38)
    - Fox Notes 5, Journals, Summary index, pp. 3000-3458, 3742-3766, 1953 (Box 38)
    - Fox Notes 7, Joffe, Tax, Miller Notes, undated (Box 38)
    - #41548 Fort Berthold File (Roll 1 A-H, Roll 2) (Box 38)
    - #45463, Fort Berthold (Box 38)
    - #49047, roll 8, Miller's Thesis, undated (Box 38)
    - Sac and Fox, Treaty negotiations, 1824-1859 (Box 38)
    - Police Records, Court of Indian Offenses, Elbowoods, Fort Berthold Agency, 1926-1936 (Box 38)
    - Fox, Historical Record #1 (Box 39)
    - Fox, Historical Record #2 (Box 39)
    - Fox, Historical Record #3 (Box 39)
    - Fox, Records of the States of the United States, Unit 1, 1840-1899 (Box 39)
    - Central Algonkian Social Organization (Box 39)
    - #49029, Tax, Miller Notes (Box 39)
    - #46685, Sol Tax (Box 39)
  - Subseries 4: India
    - #2421, Patnair & Roy, Bhubansevar Temple, Changes (Box 39)
    - #2421, Bhowmick, "First Temple of Western Midnadur" (Box 39)
    - Michell, A.N. A Grammar of Maria Gondi, (Indian Civilization) (Box 39)
    - Nicholas, Notes on Two Villages in West Bengal, 1960-1961 (Box 39)
    - Lind, A.A. Manual of the Mardia Language (Indian Civilization), undated (Box 39)
    - Trench, G.H. Chenevix Grammar of Gondi vol. 1 Grammar, Vol. 2 Vocabulary, Folk-Tales etc, undated (Box 39)
  - Subseries 5: Miscellaneous and Unidentified Microfilm
    - Ser VVVI, 1438, Dr. Will's Patient (Tape 1), undated (Box 39)
    - A01677 Zabala. Siracá y Tema Mensual, undated (Box 39)
    - Milewski's Atlas Languages of the World, "Rozmiezcenie, Jezyków", undated (Box 39)
    - MF. Collection Manuscripts American Indian Cultural Anthropology, Series IX, No. 55-64, Author's copy, undated (Box 39)
    - Carucci, et al. "Transcription of Body Motion and Speech of Frames", 3240-3269 of "Davis" [="Doris"] Film, December 10, 1974 (Box 39)
    - Birdwhistell, Microkinegraphs (Box 39)
    - Acad. Historic., Hs. De B de Jahaquin (324), undated (Box 39)
    - Acad. Historic., Hs 4812 (344 fd.), undated (Box 39)
    - Documents, Address of Welcome to Axel L. Wenner Gren, To Foodnotes to Chapter XIX, pp 962, undated (Box 39)
    - Census [Out of Focus], undated (Box 39)
    - #48359, Sapir-Laufer Correspondence, [Laufer= Sinologist interested in Asian Languages], undated (Box 39)
    - LAV #402/1965, Neg. [Cortez Ms.?] (Box 39)
    - A5535, Andrews, Richard. Introduction to Classical Nahuatl, Master Copy, undated (Box 39)
    - Hocket, Symbology for Speech, Birdwhistell Microkinegraphs. McQuown, Nahuatl Verb Complex, undated (Box 39)
    - Noticia de la lengua hueasteco, Latin/Spanish/Huesta, undated [2 Copies] (Box 39)
    - Bibliotheque Nationale, Americain #8, Spanish/Nahuatl/Otomi, undated (Box 39)
    - McQuown- No. 1942, Reynoso (Box 39)
    - #1572 [Unidentified Microfilm] (Box 39)
    - Unidentified Microfilm (Box 39)
    - "Vienna Dict." Unidentified Microfilm (Box 39)
    - "Zurich" Unidentified Microfilm (Box 39)
    - "Bancroft" Unidentified Microfilm [2 Rolls] (Box 39)
    - Escuela Nacional de Ciencias Biologicas Biblioteca- Totonac Grammar, 16th C., undated (Box 39)
    - AGI [?] 1342 Unidentified Microfilm (Box 39)
- Series V: Buildings and Space
  - Space, Evolution Laboratory, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Space Utilization Survey, 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Space, Office, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Space, Walker, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Space Utilization Survey, 1964-1968 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Space Utilization Survey, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Department Admin- Space Utilization Survey, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Space Committee- Faculty CV's for NSF Application (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Space Assignments and Needs, 1966-1975 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Space- Walker, Prior to Haskell Proposal, 1966-1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Space, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Walker Museum Blueprints, 1964 SEE OVERSIZE (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Walker Museum (Blueprint), February, 1964 SEE OVERSIZE (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Walker Museum Building, February, 1964 SEE OVERSIZE (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Anthropological Space Requirements, 1972-1977 SEE OVERSIZE (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Haskell Hall Remodeling, March-June, 1974 SEE OVERSIZE (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Haskell Hall Remodeling Project Manual, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Haskell Hall Equipment and Furniture, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Haskell Hall Moving, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Haskell Hall Rededication, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Haskell Hall, Space, Administrative Negotiations, 1876, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Haskell Hall, Facilities and Decoration, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Haskell Hall Security, 1978,1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Haskell Hall, Faculty Requests, 1977, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Haskell Hall, Correspondence I, 1974, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Haskell Hall, Correspondence II, 1974, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Haskell Hall, Committee of Management, 1979, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Haskell Hall, Remodeling Program and Technical Report, 1978, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Department. Totem Poles, 1980, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Haskell Hall Space Survey, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Space Utilization Survey Instructions, 1988-1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Haskell Hall, 1978-1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Space Survey, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - History of Walker Museum, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Teaching
  - ‘201 Committee' Committee on 201 Courses in the Social Sciences, 1934 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Syllabus of Anthropology, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Syllabus for Anthropology, Sociology, Social Sciences 240: ‘Culture, Society and the Individual', 1949 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Syllabus for Anthropology 235: New World Prehistory (Kenneth Orr), 1949 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Syllabus in General Anthropology, 1950-1954 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Syllabus, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - College: Joint College- Divisional (Departmental) B.A.'s 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - University College, 1956-1960 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Seminary, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - College: Program in Anthropology, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - College Curriculum, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - College: Anthropology Courses for Undergraduates, 1959, 1962, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Program, 1963-1968 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Courses, 1962-1970 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Syllabi, Anthropology Department I, 1960s-1970's (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Syllabi, Anthropology Department II, 1960's-1970's (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Plans, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - New Course in the College, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1975-1980 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Plans, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Syllabi- ‘Systems' and ‘The Human Career', 1963-1982 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Department- Summer Teaching, 1978-1982 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Summer Teaching, 1975-1977, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Syllabus in General Anthropology, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Outline for Anthropology 358: South Africa- Problems in Ethnology, Social Anthropology and Social Change and Misc. Class Outlines, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Series VII: Administration
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1929-1934 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1935 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Reports of Anthropology Department Research Activities, 1930-1939 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Reports of Anthropology Department. Research Activities, 1930-1939 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Copies of Master's Exams, 1935-1942 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Copies of Bachelor's Exams, 1934-1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - PhD Research Problems in Social Anthropology, Physical Anthropology, Archeology, Ethnology, Linguistics, 1938-1942 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Information on Faculty, 1929-1947 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Student Handbook and Code of Ethics, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - University College, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Press- U of C (Publication of Research conducted my Members of the Department), 1944-1949 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Saunders, H.W., University of Iowa, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Social Thought, 1948-1950 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Far Eastern Civilizations, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Eastern United States Archaeology, James Griffin ed., 1947-1951 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Psychology Department, Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Society for Applied Anthropology, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Planning Department, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - National Research Council- Fellowship Announcements, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Permissions to Reprint, 1947-1951 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Book Reviews, Fred Eggan, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Handbook for Students, 1946, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Graduates of Chicago, Analysis, 1951, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Education, Research and Training in Race Relations Report, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1951-1952 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Copies of Master's Examinations, Linguistics, 1943, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Copies of Master's Examinations, Social Anthropology, 1943, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Copies of Master's Examinations, Ethnology, 1943, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Copies of Master's Examinations, Archaeology, 1943, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Copies of Master's Examinations, Physical Anthropology, 1943, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - World Areas Research Committee, Area Center Survey, 1951-1952 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1950-1952 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Press, University of Chicago, (Publication of Research Done by Members of the Department), 1949-1952 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research, 1946-1952 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation: International Symposium on Anthropology, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Sociology Department- Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Publications Distributed by the Department (Kinkaid), 1951-1952 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Past Deans of Social Science (Correspondence with Deans Tyler and Ward), 1951-1953 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Communication, Division of Social Sciences, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Washburn Memo Re: Department, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Underdeveloped Areas, 1951-1953 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Encyclopedia Brittanica, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - 25th Anniversary Celebration, Social Science Research Building, Department. Reunion, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Reading Lists, Honorary Degree Nominations, 1951-1955 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Accounting Forms (Tama Iowa Farm, Fox Research),, 1948, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Department. of Anthropology- Misc. Correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Chicago-Frankfurt Inter-University Project (Exchange Seminar: Anthropology as an Integrated Discipline), 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Job Information, Inquiries, 1949-1956 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Visiting Professors, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Field Training- Ford Foundation Social Sciences Project #9 Minutes, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Department of Anthropology, Correspondence, 1947-1957 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Library, 1948-1957 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Program of Studies, 1951-1958 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - The Graduate Student's Guide, 1957-1958 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Program of Studies, 1954-1958 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - M.A. in the Teaching of Anthropology, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Copies of Master's Qualifying Examinations, 1943-1959 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Appointments, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Memos Re: Visiting Staff Requirements, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Division of the Social Sciences- Annual Report to the Dean, 1950-1962 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Re: Department of Anthropology Faculty, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Fallers, Lloyd, Memo, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Copies of Departmental Examination (Incomplete), 1950-1964 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1961-1964 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - University- Committee on Evolutionary Biology, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Departmental Review, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Student Faculty Committee, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1966-1969 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology Programs at Chicago, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Departmental Memos, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Anthropology, 10 Year Department. Review and Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Chairman, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Visa Information, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Schaffner Lectures- Raymond Firth, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Collegiate Division, 1965-1970 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Establishment of a Social Science- Computer Services Library, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Teaching and Research Assistants, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - University Time Schedules, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - University Time Schedules, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 1)